{
    "id": "81fe747e761f49babfb6b7c56a59dfae",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The escaped prisoner gave himself ................................... when he was cornered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "399fdb30e802497ab5e02385627ea7b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He left a letter ....................................... when he spelt his name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64ee557cc9b8481f807600fe4d31d272"
        },
        {
            "question": "Never put ...................................... till tomorrow what you can do today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0cdbdd16cbb846d3a064474aeb9f084d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must learn to put ........................................... the rising prices.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up with",
                "up",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "879e2368f5ee494ba153c3a1114a9513"
        },
        {
            "question": "He carried ............................................. the death wishes of his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4619a78b339d4daaae9f79fa9af93736"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fog passed ...................................... when the sun rose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19f31e959f2c452d9f9aed477f0579a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must provide ........................................ the education of our children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c054458afd78492ab09f3b02227e89e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am counting ...................................... his help and support.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1e6ee6dcd1d2402bb084d2244ba7979e"
        },
        {
            "question": "One must learn to cope .................................. failure and disappointments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc26a0e134104406b1b4333ae3c309af"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are looking ....................................... a bride for their son.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "69943f23f8104fc49c2a05945d1acd9d"
        }
    ]
}